eeyuva.com 2016-11-26

# EeYuva | Privacy Policy

EeYuva.com... a portal owned and operated by Eenadu Digital, a unit of Ushodaya Enterprises Private Limited (UEPL) has a privacy policy for all visitors/registered users/guests of the portal with regard to the information we collect from them and other concerns of privacy of the visitors/registered users/guests. For all online transactions we use third party services. If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, please email to us on “privacypolicy”.

All EeYuva.com visitors will be able to browse the portal, view any articles or features posted on EeYuva.com, without entering any personal information.

Some of the essential information gathered from visitors/registered users/guests who visit EeYuva.com includes, but may not be limited to, email address, first name, last name, a user-specified password, mailing address, pin code, mobile number, telephone number or fax number.

Subscribers of EeYuva.com irrevocably consent to provide leads to vendors to push ads of products that the subscriber is interested in. If visitors/registered users/guests wish to buy any online products from EeYuva.com, we may collect some additional information from them, including a billing address, a credit card number and a credit card expiration date and tracking information. The information collected from visitors/registered users/guests is NOT shared with anyone.

Except where visitors/registered users/guests are expressly informed, EeYuva.com does not sell, rent, or loan any identifiable information at the individual level regarding its customers to any third party. All information provided by visitors/registered users/guests is held with the utmost care and security. However, EeYuva.com is also bound to cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer.

**All Visitors Need NOT Pay:**  
Visitors of EeYuva.com may browse the portal, search the ads and view any articles or features EeYuva.com offer without entering any personal information or paying money. 

**Links To External Websites:**  
EeYuva.com may contain links to external websites. EeYuva.com shall not be responsible for the privacy practices of external websites and visitors/registered users/guests are advised to check the privacy policy of such third party websites. We request you to be fully aware of this when you leave EeYuva.com. Do read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.  
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by EeYuva.com

**Cookies on EeYuva.com:**  
Cookies on EeYuva.com are used to deliver various services and keep track of your personal preferences. If you do not want cookies to collect information on EeYuva.com, most browsers contain a function that allows a user to deny cookies on websites. Alternatively you can also delete all cookie files on your computer. Please note that disabling the cookie feature on your browser or deleting cookie files from your computer will render you unable to access certain features on EeYuva.com, as the use of cookies is a necessary part of the EeYuva.com technology. EeYuva.com uses cookies only to:

Please note: Cookies are used only to recollect information sent to your computer from EeYuva.com. We CANNOT access any information not sent by EeYuva.com. Some of EeYuva.com partners may use cookies on EeYuva.com (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

Changes in EeYuva.com privacy policy: UEPL reserves right to amend the privacy policy of EeYuva.com. Visitors/registered users/guests are advised to periodically check EeYuva.com privacy policy for any amends.

Any sensitive information (such as a credit card number) provided during registration/order process information, is encrypted and is protected with the standard encryption software in the industry – SSL as practiced by respective payment gateway.

Apart from using SSL encryption, EeYuva.com takes every measure in its power to protect sensitive information. Some of the staff at EeYuva.com are granted access to such personally identifiable information, needed for performing specific tasks (for example, a billing clerk or a customer service representative).

EeYuva.com uses email extensively to communicate with visitors/registered users/guests and visitors/registered users/guests may receive emails for the following services:

 **Contact EeYuva.com:**  
If you have any queries about this privacy statement, the practices of EeYuva.com, or your dealings with this portal, please email us to [admin@eeyuva.com](mailto:admin@eeyuva.com) or contact us at...  
EeYuva.com  
Eenadu Digital, a unit of Ushodaya Enterprises Private Limited,  
Eenadu Complex,  
Somajiguda,  
Hyderabad.  
Phone: 040-23318181.  
You are also advised to peruse Terms and Conditions.
